So I'm back in my image studio code here.
You can see under the system you have a folder called a C policy under which you have private and these
are the pre-built utilities.
Are they C policies return the previous APIs.
So you have these 29, 28, 27, 26 and here you have the private and public and here you can see all
those C policies written for audio.
So, so similarly we know when you create something, you can actually add it over here.
So I am now in Android Developer Portal.
So here they have you and a good documentation body selects.
So here you have all those information gierran and he had the implementation.
If you go you're going to see you can see that it's actually these things are actually stored and how
to define the implementation.
So this is a command line argument where you can set a ceiling next to a C mode.
Okay.
And here that is a lot of information over here.
I would strongly recommend you to go through this and building a C policy in building a C policy.
There are more commands starting all here, like I think in the validations or in the validation, you
can see.
So if you just grab get a B message or or the locator with ABC and then you get all the ACA denials
actually.
Okay.
So now I have open my emulator and I have a command line over here.
So we'll see what or what is next.
So violations are there in the current setup.
So if you just use this command B shell as you wrote the message grep a C, then you get all day silly.
Next, some violations actually might do it a V.C...
Okay, so you can just get it with ABC and then you get to all of them.
So let's see now how many violations out that in our look at it.
So so in order to get it from the law, can I just change it to lockout and if I do the grep over that
then you get all these errors here.
You can see that it is denied.
The creation is denied.
For this context, however, the default okay, so this is one of the label and it is the this was denied
actually the creation was denied for this one.
How they could default.
Okay.
For the class DHCP socket.
In this case it is this is B socket.
Okay.
And similarly and so all of these are denials and here you can see that perma CBC, you know, that
means kind of is enforcement more so if you want to know what mode it is actually than you what you
can do is you just get into the ADB shell and then just type get and enforce.
Then you get what is a currently it is an enforcing mode.
So if I need to set it to but we see more what you need to do is just set enforce to zero.
So then try to get the get enforce again then now it is in permissive mode.
So in case of diplomacy mode, nothing will be denied.
It'll be just there will be just a warning actually like this and it has this violation.
So now let's look and try this one thing and maybe you'll be fine.
So now you can see it's all denied but diplomacy vs one.
So that means it is it can still go continue.
You don't block anything.
It is just a warning at the moment.
So in case of war, in case when you are developing a new a new device, then you then it is good to
have it in pharmacy mode during the development during the initial development phase.
And later on then you can go through this warning and to create and AC policies and fix all of them.
Okay.
And so here here you can see all this information actually.
So this is the set in force and you can also get within the current command line just something like
this.
And there is one more thing actually that you can do.
So this order to allow this will actually automatically generate, as he likes, policies for you.
So what you need to basically do some kinds of stuff is.
So let me exit out of the shell and go first.
Okay.
So you can just pull all the AC policy things first and then know let's pull it.
So one file is no fault.
So it actually puts all the ANC policies to this file.
And then you what you can do is actually just look at.
And use this utility already to allow on top of it actually signing and then it will automatically generate
all the AC policy command line.
So why don't you have to take copy and paste so so see here.
So here this is what we have seen earlier.
Allow us to make the default whilst not having access to TCP socket.
So now you just need to define this in one of these final are the default then that will be gone.
So similarly you can put these in in it and the kitchen sink app, you can try this too.
You just need to basically copy, paste it into the basic policy files and then most of these errors
will go off.
And here you have all the information on how to write this policy.
So if you go through these documentation, I believe that is sufficient to allow for your purpose.
Okay.